Power comes in all sizes.
We Can Be Heroes is a family, action, fantasy film directed by Robert Rodriguez.
When alien invaders capture Earth's superheroes, their kids must learn
to work together to save their parents - and the planet.
Missy Moreno, played by YaYa Gosselin.
Noodles, played by Lyon Daniels.
Wheels, played by Andy Walken.
Ojo, played by Hala Finley.
A Capella, played by Lotus Blossom.
Slo-Mo, played by Dylan Henry Lau.
We Can Be Heroes is a 2020 American superhero film
written and directed by Robert Rodriguez.
It is a sequel to the 2005 film The Adventures of Sharkboy and Lavagirl.
Rodriguez was also the cinematographer and editor of the film, which stars
YaYa Gosselin, Lyon Daniels, Andy Walken and Hala Finley.
It was released on December 25, 2020, by Netflix and
received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of superhero, alien, alien
invasion, family, father daughter relationship.
The tone is lighthearted.